Hello U Hello It's nice
Здравствуйте У Здравствуйте Приятно
to meet the ingredient ladies in chat
встретить ингредиентных дам в чат
roulette I see you are an imperial and you have
рулетке Я вижу вы имперка да у вас
some kind of imperial flag Yes I understand I am
какая-то имперский флаг Да понял Я
Ukrainian I have a Ukrainian flag there are
украинец у меня украинский флаг есть
cities of Khmelnitsky imperial from where I am from
города Хмельницкого имперка откуда Я из
Siberia from Barnaul I understand Altai Territory
Сибири с Барнаула понял Алтайский край
Yes I know what you have there  not in Siberian,
Да знаю а что у вас там не по Сибирский
it’s written on the chests Paris and something
написано на грудях Париж и что-то там
else
еще
Let’s not be a
Давайте не будем
NATO country T-shirt
футболка страны НАТО
yes
да
this is a very old T-shirt from the
это очень старая футболка еще с 90-х
90s I see that you are not fresh Well there is no need to
годов я вижу что Вы не свежие Ну не надо
clarify the details I
уточнять детали
can afford to not be fresh I’m already
могу себе позволить быть не свежие Я уже
old
старая женщина
old woman I agree
старая согласен
Thanks for the compliment
Спасибо за комплимент
about the woman
насчет женщины сомневаюсь
I doubt it’s a man Well okay I think you’re an
что мужчина Ну ладно я думаю что вы
old girl but a girl Thank you I
старая но девушка Спасибо я просто я
just I just don’t believe that there are men in Barnaul I
просто не верю что в Барнауле мужики
don’t believe I don’t believe
не верю не верю
[ __ ] I [ __ ] myself
Бля я обосрался
on a date
на свидание приходит
Dude is coming now I’m going to the toilet and I don’t
Чувак сейчас я в туалет пойду и не
comes back
возвращается
Cool, this is short, my friend is so
Класс вот это короче подруга такая
awesome
[__]
Why did everyone hang this flag, what does it
Почему все повесили вот этот флаг что он
mean, what kind of flag is it? Well,
означает что это за флаг
this is the flag of the Russian Empire, they
Ну это флаг Российской империи
always ask me what they mean.
всегда меня спрашивают что означают
Well, okay, I’ll explain to you what
Ну ладно я вам объясню что
I’ve always been interested in. What does
меня всегда интересовало Что означает
yellow-blue mean? It doesn’t mean anything, they just
желто-голубой Ничего не означает просто
wrote it  blue, well,
написали синий
black are people,
черный это люди
gold is
золотой это
valor, and white is Vera. What is
доблесть А белый это Вера Что такое
valor? I just don’t know Russian well,
доблесть Я просто русский язык плохо
but you communicate very well in Russian, yes. Well,
но очень хорошо общаетесь по-русски да
some phrases like that are valor. Well,
Ну некоторые такие фразы там доблесть Ну
I don’t know what valor is. How is this
я не знаю что такое доблесть как это
in English? say that I am  I understand
по-английски скажите что я понял
in English I won’t tell you this Well,
по-английски Вам это говорить не буду Ну
at least explain what it is
хотя бы объяснить что такое
and you don’t know what valor is
а вы не знаете что такое доблесть
climb climb no
лезть лезть нет
[music]
[музыка]
Explain
Объясните
Explain clearly yes [ __ ]
Объясните четко да [__]
even a synonym this word I’m just an
даже синоним это слово то я просто
example What is valor does it mean
пример Что такое доблесть это значит
or something  adjectives there
или какой-то прилагательные там
valiant
доблестный
that this is self-sacrifice the
что это самопожертвование
self-sacrifice is the one who dies for
само пожертвование это тот умирает ради
something
чего-то да
or for the sake of someone, that is, valor is
или ради кого-то то есть доблесть это
dying for someone yes
умирание за кого-то да
approximately understood everything approximately
приблизительно все понял приблизительно
understood well Why are people black
понял хорошо А почему люди это Черные
black are people by the way
черные это люди
interesting question why
интересный вопрос почему
is this  black
это черные
because it’s a bird
потому что птица
but actually Georgiy of Belarus is always on a
но вообще-то Георгий Беларуси всегда на
white horse And who is Georgiy
белом коне А кто такой Георгий
victorious it’s like Suvorov was like yes Well, let’s
победоносит это как Суворов был типа да
not be a fool now you all
вы не будете придуриваться вы все
understand perfectly well
прекрасно Понимаете
when he lived
когда он жил
This is a saint
Это святой
Everyone once lived in Orthodoxy Not
В православие все когда-то жили Не
look, Holy Prince Vladimir, he
смотрите Святой князь Владимир он жил
once lived here,
когда-то тут
I don’t understand these matters at all.
я вообще не разбираюсь в этих делах
Well, I just don’t believe it, like I didn’t understand.
Ну просто не верю типа не разобрался
Look when the animal is Holy Prince
Посмотрите когда животное Святой князь
Vladimir, like yes there, or the Holy
Владимир типа да там или Святой
Righteous Prince Alexander Nevsky, he
благоверный Князь Александр Невский он
lived there then and there 13 And when he lived  this
жил там тогда-то там 13 А когда жил этот
St. George the Victorious and where he lived in Moscow
Георгий победоносе и где он в Москве жил
in Tula
в Туле
now I’ll tell you
сейчас я вам скажу
again you’ll start that you know that if
опять начнете что вы знаете что если
Kiev means it’s Kiev just where in
Киев значит это Киевская просто где в
what century where did this one live
каком столетии где жил этот
in the 14th century in the 14th century And where did he live
в 14 веке в 14 веке А где жил
Kievan Rus Kievan Rus 14 and 14  century there
Киевская Русь Киевская Русь 14 и 14 веке
was no longer Kievan Rus, it came into
уже не было Киевской Руси она прилетела
existence in the 13th century after the
свое существование в 13 веке после
capture of Kiev by the Mongols by the
взятия Киева монголами
Mongols by the Tatar-Mongols
кем монголами татаро-монголами
Batu And so on And this is how the water
Батый И так дальше А вот так вода
turns out
получается
Prince Vladimir then when there was a class
князь Владимир тогда когда был класс
Prince Vladimir in the tenth century in 988
князь Владимир десятом веке в 988 году
baptized Russia
крестил Русь
and in the 14th century too  his grandmother didn’t
а 14 века тоже его бабушка книги не
start the books Olga, like some,
Ольга начала типа некоторые
as I understand it,
так я понимаю
this is what I won’t say right now, but what
Вот это я сейчас я точно не скажу а чем
he became famous for, what he did, this is St.
он прославился что он сделал такой это
George the Victorious, I won’t tell you
Георгий Победоносец не скажу я тебе
anything, well, why was he made a saint, what’s
ничего Ну за что его сделали святым что
shorter than that, now he’s on the flag of the Russian
короче его вот теперь на флаг Российской
Empire  they hanged Well, just
империи повешали
like Nicholas II was made
Ну так же как и Николая Второго сделали
a saint, not so Nicholas 2 was a
святым не так Николай 2 был царь
God-anointed Tsar
богопомазанный
George is victorious, but he wasn’t a prince, it
Георгий победоносится же не был князем
just turns out he served
просто получается в Киеве служил
some prince in Kiev, what did he become a Saint
какому-то князю о чем Святой стал
about here, I can’t do anything absolutely Why does
здесь я не могу ничего абсолютно Почему
he have a horse raised there?  -the snake there
у него конь там поднятый он что-то там
just said that I
только что сказал что я вам поэтому
can’t answer you at all about this. You
поводу вообще не могу ничего ответить Я
can just look there in my
просто можете посмотреть там по моему
opinion. It seems to me that he is with a horse, he is using the spear of the
Мне кажется что он с конем он копьем
Serpent Gorynych, whether it is flowing like this or not the
Змея Горыныча протекает так или нет
dragon, or that
дракона или что
he fought against the dragon because of this.
он против дракона боролся из-за этого
I’m telling you honestly, I
я вам честно говорю я по этому поводу
can’t tell you anything about this.
вам не могу ничего
Well, I
Хорошо хорошо
won’t make up a good story, I won’t, I
сочинять не буду придумывать не буду я
just can’t answer you
просто не могу ответить по этому поводу
honestly, they answered nothing about this. Yes, good. By the way, where are
вам ничего честно ответили Да хорошо А
your ancestors from? Well,
кстати ваши предки Родом откуда Ну вот в
Barnul just wasn’t there before the Russians.  where did you
барнул лишь не было раньше русских Вы
come from Or your ancestors came
откуда приехали Или ваши предки приехали
We from time immemorial lived here on the
Мы испокон веков здесь жили на
territory of Siberia we are Turks
территории Сибири мы тюрки
you are a Turk You are
вы тюрк
Russian
Вы русская
according to your passport Russian
по паспорту русская
Who are you
Кто вы
Altaians Altaians we are the Altai terke That
алтайки алтайцы мы Алтайский терке То
is, you are representatives of the Altaians people so what about
есть вы представители народа алтайцы так
purebred Altaians no damn you
причем чистокровные алтайцы ни хрена вас
some Kostroma That’s A  you
какой-то Костромская Вот такое А вы
think that these
думаете что вот такие вот
black-eyed people are not black-eyed But these are chocks
черноглазые не черноглазые Но это [__]
Well, obviously not those
Ну явно не те
your grandmother then well your grandmother is from the
ваша бабушка тогда хорошо ваша бабушка с
Altai region from what village are
Алтайского края с какого селения бабушка
my grandparents my grandmother from the Turochak region
моя бабушка с турочакского района
lines
строчек
grandfather is also closer there there there
дедушка тоже туда ближе там
closer to Mongolia
туда ближе к Монголии
Altai language you know
Алтайский язык знаете
no
нет
Baba’s children didn’t tell you No, it’s not Russian,
Дети баба не передали вам Нет не русский
only my Russian
только мой русский
[music]
[музыка]
we have a
у нас
grandfather
дедушка
He’s a Don Cossack, I already believe this more so,
Он Донской казак это уже больше верю так
and the second grandfather on my mother’s side, the
а второй дедушка по маминой линии
second grandfather on my mother’s side, they are
второй дедушкой по маминой линии они
Crimean Tatars,
Крымские татары
and like my dad’s surname,
а как у папы была фамилия
everything in Altaian was Lapshin  Yes, it’s a purely
все на алтаец был Лапшин Да чисто
Turkic surname Lapshin, no, it’s
тюркская фамилия Лапшин нет
already
это уже
We are Kireeva
Мы киреевой
or But this is already a Turkic surname Yes,
или А вот это уже тюркская фамилия
you are mothers of Beketova Beketova Yes, this is a Turkic
матерей вы Бекетова Бекетова Да вот это
surname, yes, but the
же тюркская фамилия да
Kireevskaya surname I understand, but there are
ская фамилия понял
more of you, more of you, of
а вас вот больше больше вас крови
Turkic or Russian blood,
тюркских или русских
and how the intelligence is distributed
а интеллект как распределился
means if  the Turks mean they are stupid,
значит если тюрки значит они тупые
on the contrary,
наоборот
which means the Russians are stupid, I didn’t say Well, he
а значит русские тупые я не сказал
hinted and hinted,
Ну намекнул да намекнул
so I, too,
вот и я тоже
talking with Ukrainians,
общаясь с украинцами
come to the conclusion of Western Ukraine, I
прихожу к выводу Западной Украины
talked to people now, I’ll
общалась Сейчас с людьми
even
даже
take a sin on my soul in Donbass, I talked to
возьму грех на душу в Донбасса общалась
Lugansk anyway, they are Ukrainians,
Луганском все равно это украинцы
but they do not shine with intelligence at all
но не блещут интеллектом абсолютно
especially Western Ukraine is
особенно Западной Украины это
somehow closer to the Poles, that the Poles
как-то ближе к полякам что поляки
are wooden, that Western Ukraine is a tree
деревянные что западная Украина дерево
with the Poles, they communicated
с поляками общались
Well, for three days I had
Ну на протяжении трех дней Мне хватило
enough,
достаточно
you understand, they understand Russian very well, they
вы понимаете они по-русски очень хорошо
speak with an accent, but they understand
понимают говорят с акцентом но понимают
directly, and what for example what, for example, you
прям а что например что вот например вас
confused by the intellectual abilities of the
смутила интеллектуальных способностях
Poles, the
Поляков
Poles, they consider themselves that we are the
поляки они считают себя что вот они мы
gentlemen, we are the most important We are the best,
мы паны мы самые главные Мы самые лучшие
we are the gentlemen,
мы паны
so they are all plebeians, that is, they told you so
так это все плебеи то есть они вам так
that we are the Poles, gentlemen And you Altaians are
говорили что мы поляки паны А вы алтайцы
plebeians Yes, they don’t even know what
плебеи Да они даже не знаю что такое
Altaians are, here  such
есть алтайцы вот такие
that there are Altaians, what are plebeians, by the way,
что есть алтайцы что такое плебеи кстати
this is something from ancient Roman I remember that way,
это что-то из древнеримского я так помню
but I don’t remember that
но не помню что
there were Patricians of the plebeians, something I don’t know
там были Патриции плебее что-то не знаю
your train of thought How do you start all this
ваш ход мыслей Как вы начинаете это все
Well done Well done I really like it
Молодец Молодец Мне прям это нравится
if now
если сейчас
I have this at all  there was no and no in the
У меня такое вообще не было нет и нет в
blood I believe
крови верю
believe in the blood a little bit is completely
верь в крови маленько заложена совсем
different that to devour a man
другое что сожрать мужика
Yes, why imprison a man that well, in
Да почему сажать мужика что
general, you were in Siberia no
а вообще были в Сибири нет
you communicated directly with
вы напрямую Общались
the soldiers Yes
солдатицами Да
yes And where did you find them on the Internet
да И где же вы их нашли в Интернете
now in a cage
сейчас в клетке
from a mountain-  Altaisk also communicated from
из горно-алтайска тоже общался из
Barnaul
Барнаула
[music]
[музыка]
these are not those Altaians
это не те алтайцы
already a cross with the Mongols this is what
уже помесь с монголами
it is Black with a handle
вот это что оно Черное вот с ручкой
this is how to distinguish a purebred from an unclean one is
это отличить чистокровно от нечисток
equal to an Armenian teach and a purebred he is
равна армянина научите а чистокровная он
light brown, blue-eyed
светло-русый голубоглазый
and does not look like those who are
и не похож вот на этих которые с турками
crazy about the Turks A  where where can I see these
помешаны А где где можно посмотреть вот
blue-eyed Armenians in Abkhazia I
голубоглазых до армян в Абхазии
understood everything logically logically my settlement
все понял логично логично свое поселение
everything is logical Yes the pure Armenians in Abkhazia I
все логично Да чистые армяне в Абхазии
understood Yes
понял Да очень все Логично
everything is logical Now everything has worked out yes
теперь все сложилось да
Thank you very much of course
Спасибо вам конечно большое
it
это
means a lot
очень много значит
that I am a fool uneducated educated
то что я дура не образованная
educated
образованная образованная
you  it’s all so beautiful Well done Well
вы это так все красиво
done by the way I even like it I see Yes
мне кстати даже это нравится я вижу Да
that you get moral
что вы получаете моральное
satisfaction
удовлетворение
from intellectual enrichment
от интеллектуального обогащения
but not from enrichment of course
но не от обогащения конечно
but at least not from insults I’m just me just
но хотя бы не от оскорблений Я только я
my face showed facial expressions
только физиономия моя показывала мимику
that showed my internal
которая показывала мою внутренние
relationship to you yes yes  it was all just a
отношения к вам да да это было все прям
very real surprise, that's how you can
очень верное удивление вот так можно
say
сказать
No, it was all clearly visible
Да нет это все было хорошо видно
Yes, why eat it?
Да почему пожрать
After work, eat stress now
Я после работы заедайте стресс сейчас
a little work
немножко работы
I work
Я работаю
and I'm 64 years old
и мне 64 года
So I have the right, you have the right Yes, to
Так что я имею право имеете имеете Да
be swollen,
быть опухшей
I raised children, sent grandchildren  to
я вырастила детей отправила внуков в
school and no one for me And
школу и мне никто
where they sent my husband to
А мужа куда отправили
sleep,
спать
he’s scared, yes
ему страшно да
So something like this is an
Так что вот как то так
adult woman, by the way, older than you
взрослая женщина кстати постарше вас
[laughter]
[смех]
My grandfather was
Мой дед был
and my mother’s line was a Cossack Sotnik
а маминой линии был казацкий Сотник
who was exiled to Siberia And why
который был сослан в Сибирь А за что он
was he exiled to Siberia for  disobeying
был сослан в Сибирь за неподчинение
an order, the fact that he did not lead his hundred to
приказа то что он свою сотню не повел на
death,
смерть
I understood. But if your Grandfather, yes, was
понял А вот если ваш Дед это да был
now a military commander under Putin, he
сейчас при Путине военноначальником он
would have led his hundred to death or not.
бы привел свою сотню на смерть или нет
What do you think,
Как вы думаете
yes,
да
why didn’t he lead him then,
а почему тогда не повел
but you understand that there are different situations
но ты понимаешь что разные ситуации есть
why  then I didn’t start a
почему тогда не повел
conversation,
разговор
it’s just that the pressure is jumping on the street,
это просто давление скачет на улице
different situations,
разные ситуации
and when there are moments when you need to go to
а когда есть моменты когда нужно идти на
death, now you need to go, we walk
смерть сейчас нужно идти
on the Russian
ходим по российской
grater, well,
и мы терке ну
we are Siberians We are
мы сибиряки
Russians, Moscow is a Turkic city, no,
Мы россияне москва-то тюркский город нет
but we swore allegiance to Moscow
но мы присягнули на верность Москве
or some other  then the
или каком-то
grater swore allegiance to the Russian
тёрке присягнули на верность Российской
Empire, so ginger has not died for a long time,
империи так имбирь уже давно давно не
it still
сдохла она до сих пор существует
exists at the same time, both the Soviet Union
одновременно существует и Советский Союз
and the Russian Empire did not know about it And
и Российская империя об этом не знали А
who is now the Emperor of the Russian Empire,
кто сейчас император Российской империи
he is not there, there
его нет
is a governor, who is the governor Well,
есть наместник кто наместник
not Volodya Putin,
Ну не Володя Путин
no, interesting
нет интересно
who we got married
а кто у нас венчался
in the Russian Empire The heir to the
в Российской империи Наследник
Imperial throne literally two years
Императорского трона буквально два года
ago or three or years ago I don’t know at all
назад или три или года назад вообще не
who you
знаю кто
don’t know
не знаешь
Well, thank God Well,
Ну и слава Богу
thank you God mother, this is happening
Ну и слава тебе Господи мать творится
so that you don’t know and don’t know don’t know know
чтобы вы знать не знали и ведать не
and don’t know  we know,
ведали знать и ведать пусть не ведаем
we saw him and watched his wedding,
мы его видели и свадьбу его наблюдали
which took place in the Cathedral of Christ the Savior,
которые в храме Христа Спасителя
this is according to an ancient
происходило венчание это по древнему
Turkic custom,
тюркскому обычаю
and why is it that the Russian emperor
а почему это российский император там
got married there in Moscow,
венчался в Москве
you can go on about the emperor who
можно дальше про императора который там
got married there, it
женился
doesn’t paint this as a mega minus, but for me I just have
не красит это мега минус но мне я просто
this story about the emperor  who
вот этот сюжет про императора который
got married there two years ago Tell me
два года назад женился там Расскажи мне
this is really interesting
это интересно реально
on the Internet look at his name
в интернете посмотри как его зовут
advanced
продвинутые
You are so advanced with
Вы же такие продвинутые
one foot higher in the European Union The
выше одной ногой в Евросоюзе стоите
Hungarian Empire is there and we are there there
Венгерская империя там и мы там
is an emperor in Russia there is no
там есть императора в России нет
emperor
императора
in Ukraine and
в Украине да
the king of Britain
король Британии
you have no king
у вас нет короля
If you had a king, an emperor, a king,
Если бы у вас был король император царь
we talked. So you don’t care about the empire, the
мы поговорили Так вы не до империи
British empire is there, they have it. But
британская империи есть у них есть А
why did we sign up there
вы-то каким боком туда мы записались
as a congressman since there is no Russian empire?
конгрессансом раз нет Российской империи
You have someone Zelensky, I’m
У вас есть кто-то Зеленский
happy for you. Oh my God!
рада за вас
you don’t have a king, you
Господи ой как А у вас нету царя все у
don’t have any aristocracy Loki
вас нет аристократии Локи
spoons Now,
ложки
finally, I’ve waited,
Вот вот наконец-то я дождалась
finally, I’ve waited, Here it is, Your
наконец-то я дождалась Вот она Ваша
nature is crappy, it’s coming
натура хахляцкая
out, Here it is, it’s [ __ ], it’s waiting for
натура вылазит Вот она [__]
you, you haven’t communicated properly with the Poles yet
это вы еще с поляками нормально не
So tell me the most important fairy tale What kind of
Так расскажи самую главную сказку Что за
emperor VAZ
император ВАЗ женился два года назад
your governor Vovka Zelensky married two years ago Lenka you
Вовка ваш Зеленский на Ленке женился ты
can imagine
представляешь
it’s not from the piano there Putin’s head was
это не по пианине там Голова Путина было
on the way
он по пути
and I think that’s what it was
а я думаю что это такое было
Putin is still spitting
Путин до сих пор плюется натуру
Khokhlyatsky nature didn’t hide the [ __ ] from you climbed
хохляцкую не прятали [__] из вас лезло
climbed it will climb because  you are
лезет это будет лезть потому что вы
originally
изначально
How pitiful and [ __ ] from the inheritance
Как кушата жалко да [__] из наследства
now it’s
сейчас вылезли
just tough
просто жесть
Write a comment what it was what
Напишите комментарий что это было что
it was
это было
right at once autumn and ass
прям за раз осень а попок
[music]
[музыка]
YouTube driving us through the quarries into a
YouTube загоняя нас через карьерки в
shadow ban and duzhba is ready the video is not
теневый бан и дужба готова видео не
shown to people often
показывается людям часто показывается
information about streams is shown  in order for the
информация про стримы для того чтобы
little operatively known
мало оперативно известный
and the butts are there in a kilogram, video
а попок там в килограмме окрим видео
information and we are with you
информация и мы с вами
[music]
[музыка]